Ayşegül Aydoğan Oğuz Software Engineer

O Istanbul, Turkey

≥ aysegul.99@windowslive.com

+905377991151

ayseglaydgan

in ayseglaydogan

Profile

A Full-Stack Software Engineer with a passion for technology and innovation, particularly in .NET and React. Known for embracing responsibilities without hesitation, and recognized for leadership, organizational skills, and understanding far beyond her experience. A natural team player driven by a love for discovering new technologies and staying updated with industry trends, consistently delivering user-centric software tools that impress.

Professional Experience

2023/08 – present Software Engineer I / Infrastructure Squad

Istanbul, Turkey ING Teknoloji

Full-Stack Development with .NET/.NetCore & Java.

Transform UIs with React.

2023/02 - 2023/06 Full-Stack Software Engineer Intern

İstanbul, Turkey FORD OTOSAN

Full-Stack Development with .NET Core as Part-Time Working Student

2023/01 - 2023/02 **Software Engineer Intern**

İstanbul, Turkey Akbanl

Frontend Development with React

2021/12 - 2022/06 Embedded Software Developer Intern

Istanbul, Turkey VESTEL | Hayriya Bilişim ve Sağlık Teknolojileri A.Ş

Software Development of IoT Receiver Modem and Transmitter by using Lora as RF Module and C

Programming

Education

2020/09 Bachelor, Double Major

Kocaeli, Turkey Gebze Technical University

Computer Science and Engineering

(Droped Out)

Bachelor

2018/09 - 2023/07

Kocaeli, Turkey Gebze Technical University

Electronics Engineering (3.16 GPA)

Technical Skills

HTML	CSS
JavaScript	React
.NET / .NETCore	Java
Git	SQL
C	C++

Languages

• Turkish • English

Certificates

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador

Agile and Scrum

Design Thinking

Taken by PROJERA

Taken By Sharpware Scrimba - The FrontEnd Developer Career Path

Patika Full-Stack Development Bootcamp (On Going)

Organizations

2021/05 Introduction to the Cloud with MS Azure

Kocaeli, Turkey Instructor

A workshop about the Cloud and Azure Cloud Provider within the scope of the Microsoft Learn Student

Ambassador program

2020/10 - 2020/12 Python Programming Crash Course ☑

Kocaeli, Turkey Instructor

Programming course as a volunteer in student branch

2024/03 ING Global Hackathon
Istanbul, Turkey Attendee | InfraSquad Member

Developed a PoC project in a 24 hours about Security topic.